Nice shot, Jakah!
Yeah!
Okay, I'm next!
Sooha!
Shion! Guys!
You came to watch us practice?
Yeah. The game's tomorrow, right?
How are you feeling?
Great!
You've been missing all your shots.
Huh?
Have I?
We'll be fine, though.
We'll win again, thanks to me.
I'll dedicate our victory to you.
Huh? R-Really? Thanks.
Sooha, thanks for coming.
S-Sure.
I was born to protect you,
and I have to keep protecting you.
I'll do my best, so I hope
you'll cheer for me.
O-Okay. I really hope you win.
Yeah.
Hey.
It's dangerous for you to be here.
If you don't wanna get hurt, stay out.
Solon, are you worrying about me?
What? No!
Come on, let's practice!
Sure.
Okay, see you guys later.
- Vampire Lord -
It's been 120 years.
How have you been, Director?
Just fine, as you can see.
We thought you'd given up long ago.
We had no idea you were
still looking for us.
I didn't come for you boys.
I'm pleased we ran into
each other, though.
I see you all stayed together.
What's going on here?
We've finally met again.
I'll tell you boys, as well.
You show up outta nowhere and
want us to hear you out? Screw that!
Don't listen to her!
We're not listening.
Get out of here.
We're not the kids you knew anymore.
There are more pressing matters right now.
Khan!
Sorry for suddenly asking to meet.
Did something happen?
Well, actually...
I just really wanted
to tell you something.
I love you, Sooha.
What?
Werewolves fall in love for life.
So I'll keep loving you until I die.
I'd be really happy if you cheered for
me at our upcoming nightball game.
That's all I wanted to say.
I'll walk you back.
At last, tonight is the nightball final!
Once again, Sunshine City School
faces off against Decelis Academy!
I'll do my best, so I hope
you'll cheer for me.
I'd be really happy if you cheered for me.
What should I do?
I treasure my friendship
with both of them.
At least, that's what I thought.
But they're important to me as...
I should focus on cheering right now!
Will last year's champions,
Decelis, repeat their success?
Or will Sunshine City get revenge?
This red-hot game will
be kicking off shortly!
Mahan, Rusland, Kamil...
You promised you'd be back.
No. I have to focus!
We're going to win this game!
We'll easily beat you again this year!
Huh?
Sooha! Our team's supporters
are sitting over there!
Sooha, I promise I'll win for you.
What should I do?
The game is about to begin!
Whoa! Will Decelis score here?!
Jino! Over here!
Nice!
Sunshine hits back!
What a powerful tackle!
Shion!
Nice, Khan!
Enzy!
Damn!
Decelis scores first!
Nice, Heli.
Thanks.
Not bad!
Heli...
The first half ends with
Decelis leading by one!
That was rougher than I expected.
I hope nobody gets hurt.
Sooha!
Did you see me score earlier?
Yeah! You were awesome!
Right?
I scored our second point.
Sooha!
Our team's sitting over there!
Oh, um...
Sooha!
We're trailing for now, but I swear
we'll win, so cheer for me!
What? Sooha's rooting for us.
Sooha, our team's sitting on that side!
Hey!
Sooha's with us.
Sooha, are you having fun?
Heli?!
Cheer for us, okay?
See you later.
That's all?
Heli...
Sooha.
Do you have a moment?
- Dark Moon: The Blood Altar -
No...
That's why I've been looking for you.
No!
What? That was Sooha.
She's not there.
She's gone. She's gone.
Sooha!
Heli!
Are you okay?!
S-Sooha is...
I won't let them take it today!
I have to win!
Goal!
Sunshine City scores the goal
they desperately wanted!
Yes!
That was amazing, Khan!
Sunshine City gets revenge!
Damn.
We almost had them.
Sunshine! Sunshine! Sunshine!
Heli, is something wrong?
Something happened.
Sooha!
Why were you with Sooha?
Who took her?
Dardan, the First Vampire.
Dardan, the First Vampire? Who's that?
Could it be...
You really don't know anything, do you?
Dardan was a chancellor of
the ancient Vargr Kingdom.
Though he was originally human,
in pursuit of power,
he turned himself into a vampire
using a forbidden method.
That must be him.
You've met him?
Yeah. He attacked us with
a horde of vampires.
Who were those vampires with him?
Lesser vampires created by Dardan.
Weak to sunlight and
with no sense of reason,
they can't suppress
their thirst for blood.
You understand, don't you?
That you're different from those vampires.
You are vampire lords of
the ancient Vargr Kingdom.
Vampire lords?
Yes. You were also knights
who served the princess.
You imprisoned us!
We don't believe anything—
I wasn't imprisoning you.
I kept you at Vanfield to
protect you from Dardan.
Over a millennium ago, when Dardan's
rebellion threatened the kingdom,
the princess sent your souls into
the distant future to protect you.
However, you lost your memories
and reverted to infancy.
I tracked down every last one of you
and protected you at Vanfield House.
Princess? Wait a minute.
That princess...
Is she...
Is she Sooha?
Yes. I tracked the princess's energy here.
You must've known
instinctively, as well...
what your destinies are.
So, why did Dardan kidnap Sooha?
The same reason he did in the past.
Dardan is trying to acquire her power.
Now everything will be mine.
The princess... Dardan...
I see.
There you are, Your Highness.
Sir Heli.
The queen is calling for you.
It must be about... that.
The prince of a neighboring
kingdom proposed.
Yes, I've heard.
They say he's a great man.
But I don't want to get married yet.
And I can't promise my life
to someone I hardly know.
But I'm not allowed to choose who I love.
I'm sure you'll meet someone you can
love from the bottom of your heart.
Perhaps I should tell Mother how I...
Your Highness!
What's wrong?
Thank you, Sir Heli.
You're always rescuing me.
It's my job to protect you, Your Highness.
You look lovely as always
today, Princess Selen.
Will you be accepting
the prince's proposal?
Chancellor Dardan,
I respectfully declined his offer.
That's good news.
I didn't think you'd do as I wanted.
It's none of your business!
I agree with you, Princess Selen.
I'm opposed to political marriages.
You eavesdropped on me?!
I just naturally hear your voice.
Why?
Because I'm always listening for it.
How rude!
Rude?
Because I'm not royalty?
So status is important to you!
Unhand me!
How can I make your heart mine—
Dardan!
The next time you disrespect the
princess like that, you'll pay dearly!
He's unbelievable.
Your Highness!
Selen! Selen, please hold on!
It is as we feared.
What is this?
I believe it's due to the royal
bloodline's shamanistic powers.
Princess Selen's powers are the
strongest the kingdom has ever seen.
Her body can no longer withstand them.
At this rate, she'll die.
There's only one way to keep her alive.
We'll use the blood of the kingdom's
treasured ancient wolf god...
The blood of Vargr.
Selen!
What is this? I feel so warm...
Your Highness, you are Selen,
the princess who carries shaman's blood.
I, Vargr the wolf god,
shall grant you strength.
You're Vargr?
Selen, you're awake!
Thank goodness. You're all right now.
Mother, I met the god Vargr.
O great Vargr, thank you.
One Year Later
Mother! Mother!
Selen, don't be so sad.
You know this is the only way.
Mother...
Now that he's become First Vampire,
Dardan is trying to take over the kingdom.
The werewolves aided us,
but their numbers were too great.
So you gave them your blood...
and created new vampire lords.
Please, work together...
to protect this nation from Dardan.
But I'm just...
By drinking Vargr's blood,
you acquired the power of the ancient
wolf god and became a vampire queen.
Selen, take my shamanistic power.
My power has already been
sealed in the moon altar.
Mother...
Selen, if I die, you must hold a
coronation ceremony at the moon altar,
break the seal,
receive the queen's power,
and become the most
powerful queen of all time.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
I shall claim that power
and rule this kingdom well.
Dardan!
Princess Selen, I didn't want to do this.
I simply wanted your love, but you
wouldn't so much as glance my way.
Step back!
Marge!
So the only way to make you mine
is to take you and crush you.
Protect the princess!
Heli, get the princess!
Your Highness, are you all right?
Dardan, you bastard!
Stay out of my way!
Sir Heli!
You also love the princess,
so you must understand.
You alone should admit I'm right.
Bastard...
Now everything will be mine.
Princess! To the moon altar!
You must hurry!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Marge, your back!
Hurry... The coronation...
I can't!
I can't sacrifice everyone
to become queen!
Marge, I have a request.
I'm going to return to the palace
and send the knights' souls
into the distant future.
When the time comes,
please find them and protect them.
Your Highness...
You'll pay for this!
For you, there's no limit
to how cruel I can be.
Stay down!
Your Highness!
Sir Heli, you've saved me
from danger so many times...
without any fear or hesitation.
I know you've been hiding something...
because I've been hiding the same thing.
Next time, please...
Let us be our true selves.
Dardan tried to take Sooha's shamanistic
powers and the power of Vargr.
Yes.
I see. That legend...
It was about us.
Next time, Episode 9:
"Misty Moon: The Black Mist of Railgun."
- The Black Mist of Railgun -